Guide to the Margot Gayle Papers 1959-2005 MS 241
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV: Visual Materials
  - Photographs of cleared site under construction for Equitable Building, undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - Photographs of Gillender Building, undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - Photographs of Masonic Temple, undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)
  - Photographs of YMCA, undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder unknown container)